[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
In this module we talked about building sentiment analysis tools
在本模块中 我们讨论了如何通过分类
using classification.
来搭建情绪分析器
And now in this notebook, we are actually gonna go ahead and
在这个笔记本中 我们将更进一步
build one of those things.
亲手制作一个
So we're gonna build a sentiment analyzer for products.
我们会为产品评价搭建一个情绪分析器
So let's go ahead and get started.
那我们就开始动手吧
Okay, so here we are on an iPython notebook as usual.
好的 像往常一样 我们打开了一个iPython笔记本
And again, I'm gonna hide the header.
我还是要把标题栏隐藏
Before I hide the header, I want to change it's name, so let's rename the notebook.
隐藏之前我想改个名字 让我们先重命名笔记本
So we're gonna call this Analyzing product sentiment,
就起名叫“产品评价情绪分析”
since this is the notebook we're building, and
因为我们接下来要用这个笔记本做这个
I'm gonna hide the header and I'm going to hide
我把标题栏和工具栏隐藏一下
the toolbar just to have a little bit more space.
这样空间会大一点
And we're gonna be using GraphLab Create today so
今天我们要使用GraphLab Create
I'm going to import GraphLab to get ourselves started.
所以我要先导入GraphLab
Here we go.
开始
So the first thing that we're gonna do is read some data.
我们首先要读入一些数据
So let's read some product review data.
那我们先读入一些产品评价数据
Let me read some product review data.
让我来读入一些产品评价的数据
And this is real data set that we're going to read.
这就是我们要读入的真实数据集
So I'm gonna create an SFrame called products which uses
我先创建一个叫"product"的SFrame
graphlab.SFrame from a local file I've downloaded the data.
通过graphlab.SFrame调用一个我下载到本地的数据文件
You are going to download the data too.
你也要下载数据
And this is some Amazon baby product data set.
这是亚马逊 (Amazon) 上的母婴用品数据集
Okay.
好
We've downloaded that data, and so
我们已经把数据下载下来了
the first thing that we're gonna do is do a little bit of data exploration.
接下来我们先要浏览一下数据
So, let's explore
那么
this data together.
我们一起来看看这些数据
And this is fun.
这很有意思
So we have some product data, so let's just look at the head of this table.
我们已经有了产品的数据 就来看看数据表的head部分吧
So the head is just the first few lines of this table that I've loaded up.
head是我载入的这个数据表的前几行
And so as you can see, it's composed of three things, the name of the product.
你可以看到 它由三部分组成 首先有产品名
So Planetwise Flannel Wipes for your product.
这个产品名是Planetwise牌婴儿擦拭绒布
The review is Planetwipes are just okay but in my opinion something, something.
评论部分说"Planet家的绒布还可以但我觉得什么什么"之类的
And the rating is three.
评分是3分
And it's out of five stars so a three is kind of middle of the road rating.
满分5分给了3分 属于靠中间的评分
While the Planentwise Wipe Pouch, this reviewer really liked it,
不过Planetwise牌的擦拭布盛放袋很受评价者喜爱
they gave it a rating of five.
他们给了5分
So this is the data set that we're working with.
这就是我们要处理的数据集
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community